Agrima Pandey

Mobile: +917898925616 Email: agrima.pandey19@gmail.com

Present Address: 8 Central Road, Bhogal, Jangpura, New Delhi 110014.

Objective:

To experience and rise to a successful career in an organization where I can apply my analytical and technological skills to innovatively deliver solutions to business process. I look forward to a job that constantly challenges me to perform better.

Professional Summary:

Client-focused SAP Consultant with 3 years 3 months of providing solutions to customers. Solid understanding of the ECC, GRC and IDM systems. Highly ambitious Security and GRC consultant with background in ECC, HR, BI security and hands on experience on IDM tool. Meticulous excellent at juggling multiple tasks and working under pressure. Experienced professional with strong leadership and relationship-building skills.

Skills:

- Strong verbal communication
- Team liaison Conflict resolution
- End User Resolution Self-motivated
- Workflow Management
- Excellent knowledge in presentation,

spreadsheet, word processing applications

- Risk management processes and analysis
- Creation of ABAP Reports
- Process implementation
- Proficient with MS Word, Excel, PowerPoint,

Outlook

Work history:

SAP Security and GRC Consultant, 07/2018 to Present

HCL Technologies (Project: Vestas Wind System) - Noida, UP

Vestas Wind Systems A/S is a Danish manufacturer, seller, installer, and servicer of wind turbines. It was founded in 1945, and as of 2013, it is the largest wind turbine company in the world. The company operates manufacturing plants in Denmark, Germany, India, Italy, Romania, the United Kingdom, Spain, Sweden, Norway, Australia, China, and the United States and employs more than 21,000 people globally.

Responsibilities:

- Performed initial client assessment and analysis to begin research process.
- Performing ARM and ARA analysis for users and roles in GRC system.
- Creating, Assigning Roles and Authorizations to the users.
- Effectively analyse trace files and tracked missed authorization for user access problems and inserted missing authorizations manually.
- Creating and maintaining of users record through IDM system.
- Maintaining workflows in GRC system.
- Identifying potential SOD issues before assigning new roles to the user.
- Periodical checking daily firefighter ID logs.
- Working on EAM access management and troubleshooting the issues.
- Providing end to end user support for various BI, HR, CRM systems.
- User creation and user termination.
- Working in 24/7 support.
- Resolving tickets on priority basis in Service Now ticketing tool.
- Interacting with various teams for resolving issues.
- Engaging with onsite team in managing any new tasks / change.
- Supporting user creation and change requests.

SAP Security Consultant, 09/2016 to 6/2018

HCL Technologies (Project: Dr Pepper Snapple Group) - Noida, UP

Dr Pepper Snapple Group – DPSG is an American soft drink company based in Plano, Texas, and as of July 2018 it is a business unit of the newly formed publicly traded conglomerate Keurig Dr Pepper.

Responsibilities:

- Knowledge of User Administration, Role Administration.
- Creating and maintaining authorization and roles including Single role, Composite role and Derived role.
- User creation and assignment of roles.
- Manage user administration utilizing SUo1 and SU10 (mass changes) in creating, copying, deleting, locking, unlocking users and provisioning roles.

- Utilize SE16 and SUIM to retrieve various data.
- Analysing SU₅₃ reports
- Determination of necessary authorizations to match business requirements
- SAP SECURITY support expertise.
- Working in 24/7 support for more than 5000 users.
- Resolving tickets on priority basis in Remedy ticketing tool.
- Interacting with various teams for resolving issues.
- Engaging with onsite team in managing any new tasks / change.
- Supporting user creation and change requests.
- Managing validity dates of contractors.
- Working with user reports group wise.
- Executing and aborting jobs in UC4.
- Creating and maintaining authorization and Roles including Single role, Composite role and derived role.
- Creation of Users, Locking / Unlocking & copying of Users.
- Ticket handling-related to various issues ranging from user expiration to missing authorizations.
- Maintain password restrictions.
- Creation of mass users using SU10.
- Locking and unlocking users and analysing SU53 reports.
- Determination of necessary authorizations to match business requirements.

Network Data Senior Analyst, 10/2015 to 08/2016 HCL Technologies (Project: Dr Pepper Snapple Group) – Noida, UP

Responsibilities:

- Perform L1 level trouble shooting in network data and network voice.
- Network Monitoring of all devices and MPLS links with monitoring tools like SOLARWINDS.
- Hands on experience on Avaya and cisco phones.
- Basic trouble shooting on router, switches and wireless controllers.
- Responsible for raising incidents and logging case with vendors in case of a network and hardware issues

- Experience in basic troubleshooting by using the commands like tracer/traceroute/ping and show commands.
- Adding, Removing and upgrading the devices in monitoring tool like Solarwinds (updating the serial interfaces for all devices by using commands like show CDP neighbour).
- Experience with CISCO UNTIY MANGER and CUCDM to check and create the voicemail box for the users
- Basic trouble shooting of assigning extension, extension swap on both AVAYA and CISCO phones (TTI for AVAYA).
- Basic idea on EVM set up, conference call account (WEBEX) and voicemail settings.
- Adding new extensions in Both AVAYA and CISCO.
- Provide L1 support to customers to solve network issues.

Training Attended

- 6 month's Training at "**HCL TRAINING AND STAFFING SERVICES**". (Classroom training July 2015 to Oct 2015) (OJT Nov 2015 to Dec 2015)
- Training in Network Data Routing and Switching.

Education

B.E.: Computer Science Engineering, 2013

Rishi-raj Institute of Technology (Affiliated- RGPV University) - Indore, MP

Achievement:

• DPSG Star performer for two years.